Daniel Vinson

(650) 575-3252 390 Cypress Ave, Sunnyvale, CA

danielvinson@gmail.com Danielvinson.github.com

Professional Profile

IT Specialist with extensive experience in Computer Repair and Customer Support.

Active Directory and Exchange setup, support, and maintenance.

Helpdesk support in mid to large business environments.

Skills

Computer and server bardware, including choosing parts

Computer and server hardware, including choosing parts and construction of new systems.

Experience with RAID, virtualization, and automated backup configuration.

Network design, implementation, and troubleshooting.

Installation and configuration of Windows XP through Windows 8, OSX, and Linux.

Shell scripting on OSX and Linux.

Certifications

A+ Certified since 2002.

Work History

QA Test Engineer at OCZ Technology

03/2012 - Present

Interoperability Testing with SATA, mSATA, and PCIe devices on Desktop motherboards and laptops in Windows, OSX, and Linux environments. Bug Regression and Replication testing on all platforms. Build new testing computers and maintain existing computers.

Manage all bug testing for the Interoperability team - collect and report on all data from testing to both internal and external parties and work with Engineering or Firmware teams to ensure swift handling of bugs.

Maintain internal automation software for Windows testing. Develop, Release, and Maintain OSX automation software.

PC/HO Sales at Best Buy

06/2011 - 03/2012

Learned computer and service sales in a team environment. Improved my knowledge on customer needs, expectations, and background knowledge. Kept up with the latest and greatest in computers, printers, networking equipment, tablets, and smart phones. Worked on my skills in teaching customers with little to no background knowledge how to do some of the coolest things in technology.

Technician at Help Desk Computers

05/2009 - 02/2011

On-site and remote support and installation of servers, networks, and PCs for residential customers and businesses with as many as 100 users. In shop repair of PC and Mac hardware and software. Worked directly with customers over the phone, in store, and on site to establish and maintain a helpful and friendly professional relationship.

Designed and maintained brand new website for the company, from planning stages, through creating, and deployment. Wrote and sent a monthly newsletter to our network of 500+ customers. Created and supported multiple customer websites. Managed hosting and domains for many clients.

Education

San Jose State University

Computer Science (2007 – 2011)